http://www.internationalhifu.com/index.php/sonacare-privacy-policy

Sonacare Privacy Policy
Your Privacy Matters to Us
SonaCare Medical is committed to developing therapeutic ultrasound technologies that support precise and innovative procedures for the treatment of a range of medical conditions. It is our goal to connect patients, physicians, and healthcare providers to this leading technology, for the innovative improvement of medical applications.
By submitting your contact information to SonaCare Medical, you consent to our use of your data under this Privacy Policy.
Privacy Statement
Please read this privacy statement carefully.
This Privacy Statement explains how SonaCare Medical protects and uses the information that we gather through the SonaCare Medical website and SonaCare Medical digital marketing platforms. This Privacy Statement is intended for a U.S. audience.
This Privacy Statement is subject to change at any time and we encourage you to review this Privacy Statement each time you visit www.sonacaremedical.com or any time you submit your personal contact information.
Except as written in any other disclaimers, policies, terms of use, or other notices on this website, this Privacy Statement and the Terms of Use are the complete agreement between you and SonaCare Medical with respect to your use of this website, and any submission of personal information to the Company. You may be subject to additional terms that may apply when you access particular services or materials on certain areas in this website, or by following a link from this website.
The information we receive, and how we use it, depends on what you do when visiting our website. We collect and use your non-personal information (information that is not identifiable to you personally) differently than your personal information.
What is non-personal information?
Non-personal information is information we collect through this website that does not identify you as an individual person. It may include information such as the following:
the type of web browser software you use (for example, Internet Explorer)
the name of the domain from which you access the Internet
the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website
the date and time you access our website
which pages you have visited on our website (note: U.S. healthcare providers, please see the "uses of personal information" described below)
the search terms you use
the links on which you click
personal information that has been made non-personal or anonymized (i.e., information that no longer reflects or references an individually identifiable user)
If you visit our website to read or download information, such as information about a health condition or about one of our products, we may collect certain non-personal information about you from your computer. This information is collected from your computer's web browser: If you only read or download information on our website, we do not collect or learn your name, e-mail address, home address, or other personal information about you.
What does SonaCare Medical do with non-personal information?
Because non-personal information cannot identify you or be tied to you in any way, there are no restrictions on the ways that we can use or share non-personal information. We are always looking for ways to better serve you and improve this website. We will use non-personal information from you to help us make this website more useful to visitors. We also will use non-personal information for other business purposes. For example, we may use non-personal information or aggregate non-personal information to:
create reports for internal use to develop programs, products, services or content
customize the information or services that are of interest to you
share it with or sell it to third parties
provide aggregated information on how visitors use our site, such as "traffic statistics" and "response rates," to third parties
Cookies: SonaCare Medical may use third-party tracking and advertising providers to act on SonaCare Medical's behalf to track and analyze your usage of our sites through the use of cookies, pixel tags/web beacons, and similar technologies. These third parties may collect, and share with us, as we may request, website usage information about visits to our sites, measure and research the effectiveness of our advertisements, and track page usage and paths followed during visits through our sites. Also, these third-party providers may place our Internet banner advertisements on other sites that you visit, and track use of our Internet banner advertisements and other links from our marketing partners' sites to our sites.
The information collected on SonaCare Medical's behalf by these third parties does not contain your name, address, email address, or any other personally identifiable information. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our website may not work properly for you if you do so. We will not allow third parties other than those companies that we hire to perform services or functions on our behalf to place cookies on our website. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about cookies.
What is personal information?
Personal information is information we collect through this website and through SonaCare Medical digital marketing platforms that we can use to specifically identify you, such as your:
name
telephone number
e-mail address
city, state
job title
IP (Internet Protocol) address when such address is associated to a specific user
In some places on this website you have the opportunity to send us personal information about yourself, to elect to receive particular information, or to participate in an activity. For example, you may fill out a registration form, a survey, or an e-mail form and you may elect to receive educational material about our products and therapies.
You also may choose to allow us to personalize your visits to the website, in which case we will ask you for certain personal information to make your visits to our website more helpful to you. When this information is combined with the non-personal information that we collect through cookies (described above), we will be able to tell that you have visited our website before and can personalize your access to our website, for example, by telling you about new features that may be of interest to you.
How does SonaCare Medical keep and use personal information?
We may keep and use personal information we collect from you through this website to provide you with access to this website. In addition, we may keep and use your personal information:
to respond to your requests
to personalize your access to our website, for example, by telling you about new features that may be of interest to you
to develop records, including records of your personal information
to contact you with information that might be of interest to you, including information about clinical trials and about products and services of ours and of others
for analytical purposes and to research, develop and improve programs, products, services and content
to remove your personal identifiers (your name, e-mail address, social security number, etc.). In this case, you would no longer be identified as a single unique individual. Once we have de-identified information, it is non-personal information and we may treat it like other non-personal information.
to enforce this Privacy Statement and other rules about your use of this website
to protect our rights or property
to protect someone's health, safety or welfare
to comply with a law or regulation, court order or other legal process
Does SonaCare Medical ever share personal information with third parties?
SonaCare Medical will not share your personal information collected from this website with an unrelated third-party without your permission, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Statement.
In the ordinary course of business, we will share some personal information with companies that we hire to perform services or functions on our behalf. For example, we may use different vendors or suppliers to ship you products that you order on our website. In these cases, we provide the vendor with information to process your order such as your name and mailing address. In all cases in which we share your personal information with a third-party, we will not authorize them to keep, disclose or use your information with others except for the purpose of providing the services we asked them to provide. We will not sell, exchange or publish your personal information, except in conjunction with a corporate sale, merger, dissolution, or acquisition.
We may be legally compelled to release your personal information in response to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, law or regulation. We may cooperate with law enforcement authorities in investigating and prosecuting website visitors who violate our rules or engage in behavior which is harmful to other visitors (or illegal).
We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we feel that the disclosure is necessary to:
enforce this Privacy Statement and the other rules about your use of this website
protect our rights or property
protect someone's health, safety or welfare
comply with a law or regulation, court order or other legal process
Please note: In addition to the ways that we may keep, disclose, and use information described in this Privacy Statement, we also may keep, disclose, and use personally identifiable information that you give us through this website in ways that we believe are consistent with FDA and other governmental guidance, directions, regulations, and laws.
What happens if the privacy statement changes?
If we decide to make a significant change to our Privacy Statement, we will post a notice on the homepage of our website for a period of time after the change is made.
What about privacy on other websites?
This website may contain links to other websites. Some of those websites may be operated by SonaCare Medical, and some may be operated by third parties. We provide the links for your convenience, but we do not review, control, or monitor the privacy practices of websites operated by others. This Privacy Statement does not apply to any other website. We are not responsible for the performance of websites operated by third parties or for your business dealings with them. Therefore, whenever you leave this website we recommend that you review each website's privacy practices and make your own conclusions regarding the adequacy of these practices.
Does SonaCare Medical ever communicate directly with visitors to this website?
We may contact you periodically by e-mail, mail or telephone if you agree to that contact to provide information regarding programs, products, services and content that may be of interest to you. In addition, some of the features on this website allow you to communicate with us using an online form. If your communication requests a response from us, we will send you a response via e-mail. The e-mail response or confirmation may include your personal information, including personal information about your health, your name, address, etc. We cannot guarantee that our e-mails to you will be secure from unauthorized interception.
Are there special rules about children's privacy?
We care about protecting the online privacy of children. We will not intentionally collect any personal information (such as a child's name or e-mail address) from children under the age of 13. If you think that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, please contact us.
What about website security?
Security is very important to us. We also understand that security is important to you. We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail
How to contact SonaCare Medical:
If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Statement, please use the Contact Us form on our website.
address 10130 Perimeter Pkwy, Suite 410     Charlotte, NC 28216
phone (888) 874-4384
email info@SonaCareMedical.com
workhour Mon - Fri: 9:00 - 5:00
Latest News
17 November 2020
Read More...
31 July 2020
Read More...
Links
Contact Us
Patient Ambassador Program
Vendor Information
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Cookie Policy
Connect With Us
Search
Physicians How Hifu Works Platform Sonablate® HIFU training Overview
Peer Review Library Physician FAQ's Heat Registry Hospitals Hospital Benefits Hospital Executive FAQ's Patients What is HIFU? The Sonablate Procedure Patient FAQ's Patient Testimonials Patient Ambassadors Patient's Blog Locate Sonablate Physician About Our Story Our Mission & Vision Our Team Management Team Board of Directors News Press Releases HIFU in the News Press Kit HIFU Blogs Upcoming Events Contact
Contact Us Careers Content Library
(888) 874-438410130 Perimeter Pkwy, Suite 250 Charlotte, NC 28216
SonaCare Medical values and respects the individual privacy of all our website visitors and contacts. We have recently updated our Privacy Policy to comply with new data protection laws and to better explain how SonaCare Medical collects, uses and safeguards information collected through our website. Please take a moment to review and acknowledge our updated Privacy Policy before continuing to use the SonaCare Medical's website.
You can learn more about our Privacy Policy here.I CONSENT
